一旦两个面板在平板电脑中显示了，
Once the two panes are showing up on a tablet, let's
把我们的代码进行修改来处理列表项的点击事件。
modify our code to handle the list item click. On the phone,
在手机上，如果forecast fragment里的表项被点击，
if an item is clicked in the forecast fragment, then we
detail activity就会被打开。 在平板的界面里，如果一个表项
must launch the detail activity. On the tablet UI, once an item
是在forecast fragment被选择了，我们就通知main activity，
in the forecast fragment is clicked, we notify the main activity,
detail fragment就会被替换。这两个fragments
which goes and replaces the detail fragment. The reason the two fragments
之所以不会互相传递数据是因为我们希望它们之间能需要来维持一个虚拟抽象的概念。
don't talk to each other is because we want to maintain abstraction from
如果预报列表的fragment从一开始就知道detail fragment在它旁边
each other. If the forecast list fragment started assuming that the detail
这个设想就会被破坏。
fragment was always right next to it, then the assumption would break.
例如，手机里detail fragment 不在main activity中。
For example, on the phone where the detail fragment is not inside
那么我们的fragment必须通过它本身所属的activity
the main activity. Therefore our fragment must go through its activity and
将表项的点击事件传递到其它的fragment。
the activity must know how to dispatch the event to the other
记住fragment不一定非得在同一个activity中，
fragments. Keep in mind that our fragment doesn't always have to be
为了能够让forecast fragment可以和
used in the same activity, in order for the forecast fragment to
main activity进行交互，我们必须创建一个回调接口。
talk to the main activity we should create a callback interface. It's
更好的说法是fragment总是属于实现了
a better assumption to say that the fragment will always be within
这个回调函数的activity中，
an activity that implements this callback than to say that
而不是说它总是在main activity。
the forecast fragment will always be inside the main activity. The
detail fragment就是fragment在两个不同activity被调用
detail fragment is a good example of how a fragment can
的很好的例子, main activity和detail activity。
be used in two different activities. The main activity and the
所以我们并不依靠activity返回特定的activity类
detail activity. So don't rely on get activity returning a
使用我们这里提供的实现要点，
specific activity class. Using the gist that we provided, use a
使用回调类来通知activity：一个列表项被选定。
callback class to notify the activity that a list item has
注意一下关于表项点击的监听函数的提示
been selected. See the hint below on the item click listener.
之后activity要么打开detail activity，要么替换detail fragment
Then the activity can either launch the detail activity or
主要看当前设备是一个手机还是一个平板电脑
replace the detail fragment, based on whether it's a phone or
当你在完成这个功能的时候，你可能面临这样
tablet. When you work on this task, you'll run into
一个问题：如何把选择的数据传入
an issue of how to pass the selected date to the
detail fragment。 你会本能地去创建一个
detail fragment. Now your instinct might say to create a
自定义的构造函数来传入你的数据。但是，我们
custom constructor where you can pass in the date. However, we
通常不自定义fragment的构造函数。如果你从没转动过
don't normally create custom fragment constructors. If you ever rotate the
设备的视角，系统就不会去执行自定义的构造函数
device, for example, the system can't call your custom fragment constructor
然而他会使用一个
with the right parameters, however it can use the
空的构造方法，并且会用你之前使用的一些数据来进行初始化
empty fragment constructor and initialize it with the same bundle
所以，如果你想要把信息代入并
of arguments you used earlier. So to pass information to
初始化一个fragment，你就创建键值对的bundel，
initialize a fragment, create a bundle of key value pairs,
同时把他们设置成fragment的参数。
and then set that as the arguments on the
别把arguments bundle和 savedInstanceState bundle
fragment. Don't confuse this arguments
弄混了。
bundle with the savedInstanceState bundle.
当一个 fragment被初始化以后，你不可以改变那些
Once a fragment has been initialized, you can't change the
参数。你只能读它们，就像这里写的一样。
arguments. You can only read from them, as seen here.
换句话说savedInstanceState是为了储存fragment运行时的
On the other hand the saved state bundle is for storing information
状态信息的。你可以把它放入
once a fragment has been running. And you can populate it in
savedInstanceState 方法中。这个bundle
the on savedInstanceState method. The bundle
可以在屏幕发生旋转时，
can preserve state across orientation changes
或者fragment或activity被系统释放的时候保存设备状态。
or if the fragment or activity gets killed by the system. That's why
为什么你会再次从onCreate 或者 onCreateView 方法中得到它。
you receive it back again in the onCreate or onCreateView methods. This
当你完成后，程序应该是介个样子滴。
is what the app should look like when you're done. When you
当你选择了不同的日期，应用会更新detail 面板。你可以
tap on a different date, it updates the detail pane. You can
删除之前代码里的写死的页面数据了，
remove any hard coded data because
因为这个布局现在可以动态更新了。
the layout should be populated dynamically now.